RISHIRAM KATWAL

Full-Stack Developer

I am a Full-Stack Developer (MERN) specializing in technologies like Node.js, Express, MongoDB, and React. My focus on clean code and server-side architecture allows me to create efficient and reliable web applications. I like to play with things and learn new things to keep me updated and Passionate about problem-solving.

Contact

+977 9861334033

rramkatwal24@gmail.com

Gokarneshwor, ktm

Education

University of Sunderland

BSc (Hons) Computer Systems Engineering ISMT (2019-2024) Tinkune-Kathmandu

Sainik Awasiya Maha-Vidyalaya

NEB Science 2016-2018 Sallaghari-Bhaktapur

Language

Nepali

English

Hindi

Experience

College Project
ISMT Tinkune - KTM

2019 - 2024

Library Management System(asp.net core MVC), Hotel Management System(Windows Form), Organic Farm (asp.net core MVC), Login/Registration (MERN stack).

MERN Stack Course

Broadway Infosys

march 2023 - july 2023

I went for the MERN stack course and built an e-commerce app, where I Developed APIs and business logic with Node.js, Express.js, and React for seamless integration and enhanced functionality.

Soft Skills Technical Skills

Communication

Problem Solving

Critical thinking

Adaptability

Time Management

Teamwork

Node.js

React

MongoDB

Express.js

Bootstarp

CSS3

HTML5

Github: https://github.com/rramKatwal